the topic speech formulation uh it's
little bit using mass but it's kind of a
important and fundamental Mass I want to
introduce for this uh the uh uh today's
uh the topic in some sense for me uh
that today's kind of a basic Mass are
very important uh for us to understand
the fundamental of speech I say General
machine learning but it is important for
spe
processing so I kind of try
to put a lot of remarks of formulation
by the way not have a lot of masses but
there there are some mass that it's good
for you guys to understand and use it
for your our
problems uh and the uh this kind of the
uh the formulation is the applied to the
both end to and speech recogition and
the classical traditional hm based
speech recogition and so on and today is
Wednesday so we will also release the
weekly assignment
too okay so let's get started the speech
recogition we already discussed you know
input is web form and output is text
right and from now it's there's some
method that is accepting the web form
but usually people are starting from the
the speech features like the the uh
someone may call the the heart mscc and
so on so it's some kind of spe spectral
feature so usually we starting from this
one Z the kind of a web form so I kind
of using this other feature extracted a
representation Vector representation as
a kind of starting point but again of
course we also have a lot of studies of
the starting from web
form and the the important problem uh in
our formulation is to the con consider
the conversion from speech features or
to other sequence text sequence W and
how to formulate this problem it is
quite simple we just uh try to uh model
it as a a posterior
probability uh suppose if we have this
kind of posterior probability spech is
easy we just try to find the most the
the the likely water sequence and then
regarding it that's a kind of the speech
recognition result so it's sounds simple
but anyway speech recognition starting
from this kind of probabalistic the
decision Theory this is the posterior
and this is the maximizing so that's why
we call it maximum posteriority decision
Theory so this are starting point we may
have other decision Theory and so on but
generally that that we that good to
enough to start from the M decision
Theory and then uh the this the the
formulation uh is the more expanded uh
to see uh what kind of PW given all that
we can prepare of course this part is
very difficult uh this part is one of
the kind of major part of the speech the
recognition
part okay so to understand how to kind
of deal with PW given though let's first
start the bit kind of introducing the
mass notations
so the the since the speech condition
are handling many variables like some of
them are scar some of them are vector
some of them are other Matrix some of
the sequence so in this kind of the
slide I try to kind of unify it to using
like for example scar for the normal uh
the lowercase font and the vector for
the the Border f it can be kind of
italic or nonic depending on the kind of
the
cases but basically the lowercase board
and the uppercase board is Matrix I
think that some of the machine learning
other lectures are also based on this
kind of notations so people may familiar
with
that and the uh I usually also try to
kind of provide the
domain uh like for example this means
that this Vector o is D dimensional as
continuous
vector and the uh if uh we the the
specify the kind of the Matrix this is
kind of a written by the D * D or D
times the N or something like
that and we also have another uh Set uh
which is the
vocabulary uh that is specifying the
text and so text word and so on in the
sequence right so basically I the this
lecture we try to kind of specify the
domain as much as possible again speech
recognition is kind of a handling from
The Continuous value to the the text so
it's the very important
to uh the the set kind of domain
explicitly and in the the Set uh the
vocabulary and so on are usually using
the this the calligraphic F and also
using the the C bracket to specify the
Set uh so it's the set it's not the
sequence the set sequence difference
that there all agnostic or not right and
then the the sequence I will try to use
the kind of round bracket as much as
possible some sometimes there might be
some kind of inconen but this is kind of
the the rule that I am usually using so
the the the my suggestion of the the
presenting sequence is like
this first we can specify the element of
the sequence with the
domain and then also the the the
specifying the uh the the length uh the
the region of the sequence uh that is my
recommendation so important part is
again you know the specifying the domain
and the specifying the lenss this is
very important to the deal with a
sequence and from now on we have a lot
of sequence subsequence and so on so
that please remember this notation and
do not miss the what we have
working and then given this kind of
sequence we also often use the the
representation called
subsequence uh which I will use the this
notation sometimes o is the lower or
upper case depending on some context to
kind of unify the kind of other other
equation but basically I will try to use
the the the starting of the uh the the
index and the end of the index and this
means that the uh this is a subsequence
from here to here okay uh I think it's
slightly different from python right the
slicing way but anyway the please
remember this kind of notation
subsequence this also very important we
of can use the subsequence
notation okay now we kind of introdu the
the the the sequence notations and then
actually I just mentioned that you know
the input the speech feature all and
output is TT w p can be actually written
in the sequence form so for example
speech feature is D dimensional again
this depend on the kind of feature if we
using MCC G to be like a 12 13 or 14 and
if we using the wave form it can be of
course one uh and the the length that we
have specify and the same for the other
text part we usually de compos it word
or character right and then in this case
is this the vocabulary is a word
vocabulary and if it is a character it
becomes a character vocabulary in this
case is just alphabet and then that that
we also have a
LS over the world by using that we the
specifying the the uh the input and
output as sequence and please the good
remember this kind of notation so that
that you cannot miss that from now on we
actually have a lot of other sequence by
the way for sequence hmm State sequence
end so so always I try to kind of
provide this notation so plus the
familiar with
this okay and the other notation uh the
uh I prefer to use the operation with a
non like a log arum ma sigmoid and so on
if we type it in lat command if using
the back slash and so on uh and the um
uh index like you know the the the W the
T the n and the t is kind of a italic
but I also sometimes using the the
nonic script this is the not index but
showing that like for example this x is
from the hmm or DN or something like
that some kind specifying the type and
so on with some the natural language or
abbreviation of the natural language I
kind of using the nonic to avoid to
confuse the the the the index end the
type so this is also the rule that I
kind of consistently use in this kind of
all the slides so if you're not sure
about it please always kind of check
this slide
okay so these are kind of about the
notations uh and then I will move a
little bit more for the mass but again
it's very simple Mass so first I want
you guys to remember uh these three
rules the third one is not rule but I
kind of included the rule there so first
one is product
rule um and the second one is Su Ru and
the third one is conditional uh in
Independence assumption I believe people
know this one but I just want maybe you
guys can call it differently but I just
want to make sure that people knows this
one product do you know this that
everyone knows this one right yeah it's
kind of basic and second one Su rule it
can be by the way if it is discrete it
is Su but if it is continuous it can be
integral but anyway uh the people also
know this one right it's in our we call
it sum rule so product rule sum Rule and
then another important one is that uh
it's not actually rule but it's actually
the the way to kind of make some
approximation conditional Independence
assumption like for example in these
cases the given Z why is not important
to generating x x in this case we can
actually add removing the Y so this is a
kind of conditional Independence
assumption by the way this one and this
one uh is the equivalent and uh it can
be easily uh the proved and this would
be a one of
homework but please remember that the uh
usually uh from now on uh our lecture is
uh I try to only use these
three uh the the uh the the equations to
kind of a make some high level
formulation and then we also have
several other rules like for example
someone may heard that what is a base
rule base rule is actually derived from
the uh the uh the product rule here it's
actually if we move this one to this one
uh it becomes actually The Joint
probability of PX given pxy so it's
actually base rule of this part is uh uh
derived from the product
rule and from py is actually also the
the the by combining the product rule
and sum rule denominator is written by
like this so that many people may
remember this one this rule or this rule
but frankly I I am I am not so genius so
I usually don't remember all the rules
but I just remember these three rules
and then the the the deriving oh what is
BAS r no no no I know product R so I
actually der it yeah so same for
probabilistic chain this is also very
important the factorization method and
this actually happens the in the the
later in the how to deal with the
sequence and so on this one is also
actually combining the product rule and
recursively providing the product rule
and then we actually
Pro derive this one so again I don't
usually
remember chain rule just know or if I
forget I I kind of starting from the
product rule and then deriving it by uh
by myself so the this famous the
probabilistic rule is actually again
from this three uh Ru and there are two
exceptions that I use in my
one is a bab
approximation uh which is a kind of the
the the appears later but I just kind of
the introduce now a little bit the this
summation is sometimes super difficult
so instead of taking the summation we
taking the marks these are many people
call different but in the speech people
we call it beta uh
approximation and the also the last kind
of approximation is probably many people
familiar with this pxy or you know PX
the the px1 or py PX Z this is still
kind of a just probability abstract
probability right we want to make it our
actual problem in this case we for
example setting the gaan distribution
gamma distribution neural network two
kind of are the setting the actual dist
distribution this part is actually
probably the the people are most caring
about it in these days but anyway the
the this part and the BET approximation
is a kind of other approximation but
just kind of play with the formulation
uh we just using these three
rules and then with this the three rules
uh we can actually try to kind of do
some formulation of the speech problem
the from now by the way uh the one kind
of discussion uh why we use the
probability uh to formulate this Pro uh
problem um there are lot of reasons and
probably there many reasons would be
correct but if there someone that have
some kind of a thought or opinions or
comment about why we use a probability
to make some combination for speech
condition
is someone kind of have some other s s I
think that what you guys said usually
yes so there the things are not
deterministic right so making it the
distribution the noisy channel is quite
make Mak sense uh any other kind of
a uh comments or sort about why we use
the
probability again probably the what you
guys mention would be always correct
yeah
okay so my thought actually that yes the
things not determin that is also true uh
first for me it is very intuitive
probability intuitive zero means that
nothing happen right the one means it's
always happening so this is kind of in
intuitive and also mathematically easy
because it is bounded by the way uh the
again you know uh we do not have to the
probability we can do everything in the
continuous space and then just
everything as a regression we could
probably make speech conition uh but uh
the bounded uh structure is actually
good to Nature so that we actually often
use this kind of
representation uh instead of the
regression bounded value is easy
toedit and also easy to interpret and
the third one is easy to
formulate so uh the especially you know
just a continuous value and regression
without constraint it is very difficult
to set what kind of a constraint we
should do but the the probabilistic
cases we basically the H three
formulation that I mentioned by using
this three formulation we can actually
make some kind of reasonable the
formulation uh which is also intuitive
and so on so uh the from now on I try to
use the only product sum rules and
condition independent assumption to uh
the the formulate the speech equ problem
of course this is high level formulation
after that we need to kind of providing
it as actual function like a gaan DNN
and so on that is a different part but
high level formulation we just using
this product sum and condition
independent assumption to the the uh the
the make our problem to be
formulated so I will explain some of the
example so first one are the enter and
speech recognition by way enter and
speech
recognition uh the is actually doesn't
use so much about this kind of
formulation so mostly we just replacing
this pwo other kind of neon Network
function although data I will explain
bit more the detail usually we use a
probabilistic chain R to factorize the
problem but the uh the other the the
formulation we basically don't use
instead we try to use a sophisticated
neural network to solve the problem and
it was kind of a nowadays the quite kind
of a popular and it's actually the
thanks to the Advance in the the newer
Network like attention CTC and so on uh
it is actually not so difficult as used
to be but before that we actually have a
difficulty of directly solving this PW
given all so that we try to kind of
using some kind of Mass to make the
problem tractable that is a kind of
classical method based hmm uh the the
speech condition so I call the end to
end speech condition and hmm based the
the speech condition uh as a kind of
Distinction and the traditional method
is I again I call hm based speech
function but it's actually having a lot
of difference like the mostly hm based
speech function is using a p for end to
end the speech doesn't use P him or
something like that there are several
differences but just to simplify the
kind of naming I just call the
traditional method hm based Spees in
this lecture
okay okay so hm based uh the speech
conition uh is actually uh the quite
different it's actually the uh the
decomposed problem uh into the several
component feure extraction would be
again probably same similar the speech
part can be a de compos three the
component and I will explain this kind a
little bit more
detail so first uh the the the problem
from the the speech features to the text
sequence was used to be very difficult
due to the kind of a small amount of
data was less powerful the machine
learning tools like we didn't have a
good new network tools and so on so
instead of directly converting speech
features to text we actually try to put
some intermediate
there that is
funny it's very kind of reasonable right
when we also learn the kind of language
we also try to kind of pass the land
kind of a the the instead of the land
the actual kind of surface
representation we also check the kind of
how it is
pronunciated based on the pon
representation right and initial spee is
actually highly using this kind of
knowledge and some of the method are
still using this phing based
approaches and then how to introduce the
pH de a in the this PW given law as you
can see this one doesn't have actually
any
information uh about the fing sequence
right and
then as I mentioned that we can use a
three of three rules one of the three
rules first we introduced the The Forum
sequence corresponding to the word
sequence which is you know are the not
like a word vocabulary or character vo
vocabulary this is kind of the the pH
pronunciation the the vocabulary and
then this also has some own LS right
first we kind of introduce this kind of
Pon sequence and how to incorporate this
to this other the PW given all and then
we actually using uh this
method and uh can use uh make the
today's first one the uh the short quiz
so first short quiz from here to here I
use the the one of the uh the
rules uh among
three uh and which one uh do we
use product rule bet approximation
condition Independence assumption uh the
Su rule this not sub sorry Su rule uh
which one uh do we use that is a kind of
question okay so the
um there are several uh mistakes
the half of people actually made a
mistakes uh the answer is Su
Ru so uh from here to
here uh we just introduce this kind of
uh the uh for
sequence and then taking the summation
it goes to PW given this is a kind of
typical sum rule so please remember that
if you try to kind of include
additional sequence of Val variable how
to do that mathematically we just using
the sum rule
okay next line this is also second
question can you
open same question but from the second
line
to third
line uh the F rule that we should use
it's actually a little bit complicated
but it's actually one of them just one
of
them the answer is product rule we just
only using the product rule and then
derive this
one uh and then actually the ARA is
about the W so the denominator we
usually can uh remove it right and then
last one uh is also question
yeah from the thir line to Fourth right
uh the uh which one uh we
used this one and this one the same this
one this one the same this one this one
is different right
and what R we
use many people uh did the correct
answer yeah this is conditional
Independence
assumption um three rules to the
factorize uh the three distrib uh one
distribution to the three
distribution so this kind of a the
procedure is the very
important uh by doing that we can
actually make the program uh the the
modularize and factorized and
productable so please remember uh this
uh the the high level operation even in
the neural network ERA this kind of way
of thinking is very
important and this uh the method it's
also the called Noy Channel model Noy
means the kind of distribution uh the
instead of the directory solving this
one we consider that both o and W is
kind of distribution and then finally
are presenting these three distributions
and this one the first one is called
acoustic model and the second one is
called rexan and the third one is
language model it can be nram or Ag and
acost model can be AGM but now that most
of them are actually reped with a neural
model uh and so on and by the way uh
this method is uh not only applied to
speech many of the sequence to sequence
models we actually using it so actually
machine translation also using the same
formulation so originally the the speech
conition and the Machine translation
people are kind of the same uh the group
and actually creating the uh data using
the same methodology to realize the
speech recognition and the Machine
transl
in the beginning of the the the the
speech and the NLP the research error in
19 the 70s or
80s okay so uh this is a kind of a three
factorization now so uh this uh the the
the acoustic modeling Lex language
modeling is actually converting the
speech features to pH sequence and the
next going to are converting the word
sequence and then finally language model
to define the kind of output and this is
the originally I used the O and W and
just starting from PW given o but by
using the uh the the the product rule Su
Rule and conditional Independence
assumption we can factorize this problem
and this each of the distribution are
corresponding to the kind of problem
that that we want to solve so this
methodology uh is very important first
the
factor very good question this is more
like assumption approximation we saw
that this is a very good approximation
and we use it however uh it is very good
question yeah I think I should mention
it uh the P the the yes the the
observation speech features could be
mostly depending on the P but it can
also be depending on the kind of a word
context and so on right right so this
actually the conditional Independence
assumption is just one of the
approximation it's not very bad right
it's reasonable so we often make it by
the way if we don't use the conditional
Independence assumption this problem is
the from the here to here it's
equivalent right mathematically this one
and this one is completely equivalent
and actually difficulty also that is
equivalent solving this this one and
solving this one is the the almost same
however by setting the conditional
independent assumption again it's not
very bad right the speech features only
depending on the the P it is not bad so
by using this kind of assumption we can
make this the problem to be more kind of
a tractable so condition where and how
we use the conditional Independence
assumption is very important and then
later we will use it for the hmm or CTC
or and so
on okay so yes this is actually exactly
this part the condition inous assumption
is actually I say that more like our
kind of assumption modeling
approximation part so it is not unique
uh it is most the mostly based on our
kind of sense uh to make it but by using
this kind of the methodology we can
actually make the problem tractable so
that is the kind of other way we kind of
develop for the classical hm based that
speech
recognition Okay so now I kind of
explain about each of the block the more
kind of little bit detail but it's still
shallow the following lectures are
explain for example one of the lectur is
that are discussing the feature
extraction and many of the lectures are
they discussing about about acoustic
modeling language modeling and so on but
today I will give you some VI of what
the the each of the module are doing
first the feature extraction part that
is a kind of the beginning of the our
kind of the process uh this is actually
uh the the mostly the based on the
signal processing method like a m
frequency caps quent and other kind of
other
method uh and so one and the the time
scale is are very different web form is
actually very kind of the the the fine
resolution signal right it's the the 16
khz or 48 khz is that the waveform that
we usually use which means that the 1
second is represented by the
48,000 the sequence right uh that or 16
khz that we usually use this is very
kind of small at the time scale but the
fure extraction is converting it to more
like the still of little bit smaller but
the tractable the time scale like a 10
millisecond and so on that is kind of
important because the many of the ph and
so on is changing this time scale and
then that the converting the kind of one
dimensional the signal to the the 12 to
40 uh dimensional Vector uh that is a
kind of the speech feature there's lot
of kind of the property of how to kind
of convert and so on which I will
explained in the lecture for but anyway
this is know similar to the other
machine learning problem just a first
that front end processing to converting
the the low signal to the the the
features that we are kind of easy to tr
the deal with and the second part now we
kind of converting the this time domain
waveform to the the vector of the
sequence and then acoustic modeling is
converting the kind of this feature to
the possible pum sequence so this part
is actually one of the most important
part in speech most kind of performance
comes from this other component and then
here people are using hmm and gaan
mixture model or later people started to
use hmm and deep neural network and so
on so this lecture try to cover the the
traditional one to the the latest one so
we will cover the GMM and the DNN both
formulations uh and so on and then it's
actually the the the converting the
the time frame the the features to the
the pH sequence so it actually has a big
jump so before that it is you know eal
at 10
millisecond the signal but for it can be
actually changing the duration depending
on the kind of uh the phon type or
context so it's actually becomes the the
symbolic the sequence from the kind of
physical the sequence so this part is
actually one of the the big changes in
the the the speech processing and
basically they are not converting one by
one all kind of probabilistic this means
that they they this acoustic modeling
providing the pum sequence with some
probability or some likely to score and
then data processing taking this kind of
a other soft decision and then further
kind of enrich this kind of other
hypothesis so this is a kind of acostic
modeling part
and then third part is lexicon part and
this part is actually not so much
probabilistic most of the people are
just using the the the one to one or one
to many mapping or some some languages
many to many mapping but the pH from pH
to we convert it to the kind of word
sequence and basically what do how to do
that we basically using listic resource
this
and then converting it again you know
sometimes one to many or many to many
little bit complicated but English cases
mostly it's not so difficult and uh but
to make this kind of things of course we
need a pronunciation dictionary right so
that is kind of a the resource we have
to use so if
we apply this method to the low resource
languages where we might not have so
much Rich pronunciation dictionary it
can be an
isue and the uh I can skip this part and
maybe I can also skip this
part okay so the uh the pronunciation uh
dictionary uh the actually one of the
most famous pronunciation dictionary
that is used for speech recognition is
CMU dictionary it's actually developed
and maintained here the professor Alex
roniki is still maintaining it so if you
have some issues in the the CMU
dictionary you can actually send email
to him and then he can deal with it so
today I actually want you guys to play
with uh not today that other kind of
weekly assignment I want you guys to
play with a little bit about it but
maybe I can play that with that this a
CMU
dictionary there a lot of cool interface
and so on but basically the if you the
some this a web interface uh if we type
the some kind of a the word and then the
CM dictionary providing the other for
sequences and the
yeah
uh
U okay emu is converted to
CM okay
cool and
the
next let's type w my
name do you think it is included in cm
dictionary it's actually
included VAV is very kind of common name
in Japanese so that's why probably it is
included okay let's test my name
first
name H I N
I do you think it is
included you guys have a good guess
nothing dictionary my name is not
included so I may ask Alex Niki to
include
it and actually uh the this many the
vocabularies are covered but some of the
vocabularies are not covered like
what kind of the vocabul what kind of
word do you guys imagine that is not
included because very kind of
complicated one is not definitely
included but even common very popular
word it sometimes not
included yeah that's may not be included
or may be included uh the uh the the my
kind of the the good example is
covid-19 of course it is not included
why it is too new yeah of course if we
you know frequently update dictionary
it's going to be included but a new one
basically it's not easy to update if
someone very frequently updated uh it is
included but if not it is I used to use
the the the word
Bitcoin Bitcoin also is not included but
Bitcoin we can easily you know guess the
kind of a pronunciation right so uh but
this is a kind of a issue in the
dictionary based approaches if it is not
included we cannot get the kind of dire
so we need some kind of a ways to solve
this one and there's some kind of
advancement like a graph to H uh the the
the tool kit to providing such kind of a
uh the pronunciation and so on but
basically the other than that we
actually the highly ring on the the
dictionary whether it is CM dictionary
or other language a dictionary resource
in the language and so on so these are
kind of Le comp part and in my lecture
lexcom is not included in the detail so
it's it is kind of everything about very
good question actually some of the tools
are providing the pronunciation based on
the
context so uh the for example actually
uh the uh yes that it also happened
often happen in the English but other
languages this is happen everywhere uh I
know my language Japanese which is
actually quite the
contextually first the each of the
character has a two to three
pronunciations always and this
pronunciation is changing depending on
the kind of context so that like that
you said read and that it's dependent
context right but the Japanese Cas is
it's all almost always all the character
is happens so actually how to do that we
actually uh instead we have some
dictionary but how to get this kind of
pronunciation we usually using a machine
learning tools like the CRF or deep NE
Network and the the throwing the entire
text and then getting the context and
then providing the kind of a best kind
of a pronunciation and word boundary and
so on so the the uh the some of the
tools actually require such kind of
context but this the the English cases
just have for example multiple
pronunciations and given the multiple
pronunciation we just kind of providing
the several kind of candidate uh of the
the the uh the the the corresponding
word and then uh this can be uh the
dater the with the language model to be
this
and then get the final result so the
basically the dictionary based approach
is mostly working in English
Especial okay in the last part language
modeling which I also try to kind of
make it quickly so language modeling now
the very popular famous right PW and the
using the auto regressive Transformer or
whatever to kind of a the producer kind
of the probability uh the and so on so
this the language modeling is actually
originally often studied in speech and
machine
translation actually I I did not expect
that now you know language model itself
becomes super popular so it used to be
the language model is mostly supporting
the some of the kind of the
sequence generation problem especially
in the speech the machine translation so
the the the language model in the speech
context is also kind of in to kind of
providing the more kind of the the
natural language variations and the
nowadays again it's mostly based on the
neural but the the more kind of
intuitive way is the people are also
using the count and then it is very
natural that for example goto can be at
this kind of three uh the uh the uh the
the
phrases but uh I actually check this the
37,000 of the war Street Journal are the
sentences and then I found that the goto
appeared 51 times in this kind of a
corpers and other go two and go to uh do
you guess how many times it
appeared actually it's zero
yeah yeah it doesn't appear so it's very
natural right because this is a you know
Common phrase so this means that the
it's nowadays now again it's neural but
the the more intuitively used to be
people using counter base but anyway the
language modeling is try to kind of
providing the most
likely the the the the the world kind of
the sequence given the kind of this kind
of three patterns so acoustic modeling
providing and Le providing totally three
kind of this kind of candidate and then
if using a language model we can select
go to right it is very
natural however it is not the everything
actually this the zero is a very kind of
a difficult problem because zero means
that that it becomes zero probability so
I said that it doesn't in the the in
37,000 sentences but if we including
this one to the Six
Million actually the the it will be
different go to still kind of quite
often happens
2000 two more than 2,000 times and the
go to actually appear two times okay
yeah there one example here go go 200
yeah it's not very natural sentence but
it's actually that happened so we should
not set a zero probability at least we
should provide some probability right so
this is a kind of the difficulty of the
language model this actually 40 one
times this
appeared and most of the cases go too
far this the the phrase appear the
mostly and then again that the
previously it was Zero uh but the uh uh
if we have our kind of the more patterns
more kind of samples we actually have
our the lot of the uh at least not zero
probability so this means that we have
to providing uh some probability not
just you know taking the uh the most
likely one but the at least providing
some probability otherwise the this uh
the sentence uh does not
appear okay so uh this is kind of the
speech again that each of the component
I
will explain bit more the one by one in
the following lecture but we have a
feature extraction acoustic mod Lex
language modeling and each is the method
is based on the different kind of
computational method so used to be it
was very difficult to build a speech
condition uh but nowadays it's actually
becomes the end to endend the speech
conition so in our kind of lecture again
I will also explain about some part in
the classical which is still important
to understand our speech problem but the
mostly we are also working on the
the teaching the I'm Al mostly teaching
the end to end the speech part that is
also very kind of exciting uh by
following the recent Trend in uh deep
new network